Johannes: fix: make navigation more user-friendly (#7599)
Bhagya Amarasinghe: fix: support OTEL host config for envoy telemetry (#7692)
Anshuman Pandey: feat: custom posthog events (#7647)
Salim B: docs: remove spurious left-overs (#7690)
Bhagya Amarasinghe: feat: add envoy gateway helm bundle (#7686)
Tiago: feat: Supporting different AI providers within Formbricks (#7611)
Anshuman Pandey: fix: merge epic/improve-telemetry into main (#7666)
Tiago: chore: Revoke all active sessions after password reset (#7628)
Johannes: fix: multi-lang toggle covering arabic text (#7657)
Johannes: fix: 7549 multilang button overflow (#7656)
Tiago: fix: harden api error reporting for v2/v1 Sentry observability (#7633)
Dhruwang Jariwala: fix: prevent language switch from breaking survey orientation and resetting language on auto-save (#7654)
Anshuman Pandey: fix: adds formbricks instance on window (#7630)
Matti Nannt: chore: add Codex environment config (#7589)
Matti Nannt: docs: remove non-official self-hosting options from README.md
